checkoutspy.com 2019-04-06

# CheckoutSpy.com - Privacy Policy

## Who we are

We are CheckoutSpy and this policy covers all our websites. We are committed to protecting personal data in compliance with all applicable laws, rules, and regulations.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Contact forms

We have provided contact forms for you to contact us. We will use the information provided by you only for the purposes of your communication.

### Cookies

We use cookies on our websites. For more information, please see our [cookies information page](https://www.checkoutspy.com/cookie-policy/).

### Service Provision

In order to provide our services and contact you, we obviously need a name, email address, password, company name and other such contact details. We will also require invoicing details.

## Domain names and privacy

Domain names are not personal data, however domain registration information may contain personal data linking you to the domain names you own. We recommend that you check with your registrar regarding their privacy policy or their privacy services.

## Who we share your data with

We will not share or sell any personal data with third-parties. Only authorized personnel have access to your information to service your account.

## How long we retain your data for

Whilst you have an account, or as required to provide services to you and to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our terms and conditions.

Non personal information will be stored on Google Analytics for 26 months.

## What rights you have over your data

You can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

If you have an account with us, you can edit your personal account information when logged in.

## Where we send your data

No personal information will be sent anywhere. They are stored with 3rd party service providers (hosting, data centers) with whom with have agreements regarding data security.

## Your Rights

  * The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used
  * The right to access the personal information we hold about you
  * The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you
  * The right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances 
  * The right to stop direct marketing messages and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at any time 
  * The right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service provider 
  * The right to complain to your data protection regulator

## Questions & Contact information

Feel free to contact us anytime if you:

  * Have any questions or feedback about this privacy policy
  * Would like us to stop using your information
  * Want to exercise any of your rights as set out above, or have a complaint

You can contact us [here](https://www.checkoutspy.com/contact-us/) or if you’d like to, you can write to us at:

CheckoutSpy, Unit 10225, PO Box 6945, London W1A 6US

_Last updated May 2018 to address  the European Union General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"), which will take effect on May 25, 2018. This data protection law replaces the 1995 Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC)._
